Guide to the Todd-Bingham Picture Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- GLASS NEGATIVES AND LANTERN SLIDES, [ca1870s-1910]; Series III; 17 linear feet (121 boxes)
  - Glass Negatives
    - United States
      - Massachusetts
        - Amherst
          - Amherst Historical Society
            - interiors (Box 84, Folder 854-861)
          - Residences
            - "The Dell," interiors 1887-1896 (Box 84, Folder 862-867)
            - Observatory House
              - exteriors (Box 84, Folder 868-869)
              - interiors (Box 84, Folder 870-877)
              - interiors (Box 85, Folder 878-881)
              - "Davis plates of the home" (Box 85, Folder 882-892)
          - Views (Box 85, Folder 893-894)
          - Amherst College
            - "Panoramas from Dome" 1908 Dec 22 (Box 85, Folder 895-900)
            - President's house (Box 85, Folder 901)
          - Miscellaneous and unidentified
            - House(?) (Box 85, Folder 902)
            - Time Ball, New York City (Box 85, Folder 903-905)
            - San Fabian, Chile (?) (Box 85, Folder 906-911)
              See: box 161 box 165
    - Astronomy and textbook material
      - Asteroids (Box 86, Folder 916-917)
      - Book illustrations— New Astronomy
        See also: Box 85, #906
        Box 88, #1007-1027
      - General (Box 86, Folder 918-923)
      - General (Box 86, Folder 924-953)
        See: box 162
      - Book illustrations— Stars and Telescopes
        - Comets
          - Diagrams (Box 86, Folder 954-956)
          - Donati's Comet 1843, 1858, 1865 (Box 86, Folder 957-959)
          - Great Comet of 1882 (Box 86, Folder 960)
          - Halley's Comet—tapestry (Box 86, Folder 961)
          - Swift's Comet (Box 86, Folder 962)
          - Unidentified—unpublished (Box 86, Folder 963-965)
          - Unidentified—unpublished (Box 86, Folder 966)
        - Eclipses
          - Archaelogical subjects (Box 87, Folder 967-969)
          - Castori (Box 87, Folder 970-981)
          - Corona, 1878 Jul 29 (Box 87, Folder 982-983)
          - Corona, 1889 Jan 1 (Box 87, Folder 984-985)
          - Corona, eruptive prominence 1895 New Astronomy (p. 282) (Box 87, Folder 986)
          - Corona—Russia, 1914 (Box 87, Folder 987)
          - Corona 1918; Jun 8 (Jolls plate?) (Box 87, Folder 988)
          - Corona—Tripoli (?) (Box 87, Folder 989-992)
          - Corona—unidentified (Box 88, Folder 993-1000)
          - Corona—(#1002-missing) (Box 88, Folder 1001-1003)
          - Corona—oversized (Box 88, Folder 1004-1006)
            See: box 172A
          - Phases— New Astronomy (pp. 255-304) (Box 88, Folder 1007-1027)
          - Phases—New Astronomy (pp. 255-304) Sun's surface (Box 89, Folder 1028-1035)
      - Equipment (Box 89, Folder 1036-1044)
      - Observatories and telescopes
        - Africa, South—Capetown (Box 89, Folder 1045-1048)
        - France—Paris (Box 89, Folder 1049-1051)
        - Germany—Pottsdam (Box 89, Folder 1052)
        - United States
          - California (Box 89, Folder 1053-1064)
            See: box 163
          - Massachusetts—Amherst College
            See also: box 167
            - Arrival of telescope for new observatory—1905 May 4 (Box 89, Folder 1065-1067)
            - Construction of new observatory (Box 89, Folder 1068)
            - Interiors of new observatory (Box 89, Folder 1069-1071)
            - Lawrence Observatory (Old Observatory) (Box 89, Folder 1072)
            - Unidentified telescope—scale model (Box 89, Folder 1073)
            - Unidentified telescopes (Box 89, Folder 1074-1075)
      - Planets and satellites—New Astronomy, (pp. 305-370)
        - Jupiter (Box 90, Folder 1076-1077)
        - Mars (Box 90, Folder 1078)
        - Mercury (Box 90, Folder 1079-1080)
        - Meteorites (Box 90, Folder 1081-1082)
        - Moon (Box 90, Folder 1083-1086)
        - Saturn (Box 90, Folder 1087-1089)
        - Uranus (Box 90, Folder 1090)
        - Venus (Box 90, Folder 1091-1093)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 1094-1096)
      - Spectra (Box 90, Folder 1097-1100)
      - Stars
        - "Aries in Center," 1888 Mar 8 (Box 91, Folder 1101)
        - "Belt of Orion," five minute exposure Parvin telescope lens (Box 91, Folder 1102)
        - "Milky Way, E. E. Barrows, Lich Observatory," (Box 91, Folder 1103-1105)
        - "Nebula 4,"—C2237 enlarged three times, E. E. Barrows, Lich Observatory (negative missing) (Box 91, Folder 1106)
        - New Astronomy (Box 91, Folder 1107-1114)
        - Unidentified (Box 91, Folder 1115-1119)
      - X-Rays and miscellaneous
        - X-rays (Box 91, Folder 1120-1131)
        - X-rays (Box 92, Folder 1132-1137)
        - Zodiac drawings (Box 92, Folder 1138-1139)
        - Filmstrip—unidentified houseboat (Box 92, Folder 1140)
  - Lantern Slides
    - Africa, North
      - Tripoli, 1900
        - General (Box 93, Folder 1-20)
        - General (Box 94, Folder 21-40)
        - General (Box 95, Folder 41-45)
        - General—negatives missing (Box 95, Folder 46-47)
        - Eclipse expedition—coronas and map (Box 95, Folder 48-52)
      - Tripoli, 1905
        - General (Box 95, Folder 53-60)
        - General (Box 96, Folder 61-80)
        - General (Box 97, Folder 81-83)
        - Eclipse expedition (Box 97, Folder 84-86)
      - Africa, South
        - Capetown (Box 97, Folder 87-89)
        - Kimberly (Box 97, Folder 90-97)
        - Kimberly (Box 98, Folder 98-99)
        - Unidentified (Box 98, Folder 100-103)
      - Africa, West
        - General (Box 98, Folder 104-113)
        - General (Box 99, Folder 114-116)
        - Angola, 1889
          - Eclipse expedition
            - Coronas (Box 99, Folder 117-119)
            - Eclipse path—diagrams (Box 99, Folder 120-121)
            - Equipment (Box 99, Folder 122-124)
            - "Pensacola" cruise—general (Box 99, Folder 125-128)
          - "Pensacola" cruise—general (Box 100, Folder 129-31)
          - "Pensacola" cruise—maps
            - Route of expedition (Box 100, Folder 132)
            - Ascension Island (Box 100, Folder 133)
            - Barbados (Box 100, Folder 134)
            - Bermuda (Box 100, Folder 135)
            - Capetown, Table Bay (Box 100, Folder 136)
            - Horta (Azores) (Box 100, Folder 137)
            - Porto Grande, Cape Verdas Islands (Box 100, Folder 138)
            - Rio Cuanza (Box 100, Folder 139)
            - Scabed chart (Box 100, Folder 140)
            - Sierra Leone River (Box 100, Folder 141)
          - "Pensacola" cruise—newspapers
            - O Acoriano (Box 100, Folder 142)
            - Barbados Agricultural Reporter (Box 101, Folder 143)
            - Barbados Globe (Box 101, Folder 144)
            - O Futuro d'Angola (Box 101, Folder 145)
            - Muen'exi (Box 101, Folder 146)
            - The New Era (Trinidad) (Box 101, Folder 147)
            - St. Helena News (Box 101, Folder 148)
            - Sierra Leone Weekly News (Box 101, Folder 149)
      - Ascension Island (Box 101, Folder 150-152)
      - Azores (Box 101, Folder 153-157)
      - Cape Lido (Box 102, Folder 158-159)
      - Loanda (Box 102, Folder 160-164)
      - Rio Quanzo (Box 102, Folder 165-166)
      - St. Helena (Box 102, Folder 167-171)
      - St. Helena (Box 103, Folder 172-185)
      - St. Helena (Box 104, Folder 186-195)
      - Sierra Leone (Box 104, Folder 196-197)
    - Canada
      - General (Box 104, Folder 198-200)
      - General (Box 105, Folder 201-213)
      - General (Box 106, Folder 214-221)
    - Chile, 1907
      - Alianza (Box 106, Folder 222-234)
      - Desert of Tarapaca (#237 destroyed)
        - General (Box 107, Folder 241-252)
      - Opposition of Mars
        - Arequipa Station (Box 108, Folder 253-254)
        - Equipment—telescopes (Box 108, Folder 255-268)
        - Mars (Box 108, Folder 269-271)
        - Unidentified and miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 272-275)
    - Dutch East Indies
      - Singapore—views (Box 109, Folder 276-281)
      - Singkep—views (Box 109, Folder 282-289)
      - Sing Kep—views (Box 110, Folder 290-306)
      - Sing Kep Expedition
        - Eclipse path—maps (Box 110, Folder 307)
        - Equipment (Box 110, Folder 308-309)
        - Group portraits (Box 111, Folder 311-313)
    - Egypt
      - People (Box 111, Folder 314-315)
      - Suez Canal (Box 111, Folder 316)
    - Germany
      - Oberammergau—Passion Play, 1900
        - Performers (Box 111, Folder 317-329)
        - Performers (Box 112, Folder 330-349)
        - Performers (Box 113, Folder 350-369)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 370-376)
    - Japan
      - "In Ainu Land," Mabel Loomis Todd slide lecture
        - Native life, 1896 (Box 114, Folder 377-388)
        - Esashi—general
          - People (Box 115, Folder 389-396)
          - Places (Box 115, Folder 397-403)
          - Places (Box 116, Folder 404-411)
        - Esashi—eclipse expedition, 1896
          - "Coronet" (Box 116, Folder 412-419)
          - Equipment (Box 116, Folder 420-421)
          - Group Portraits (Box 116, Folder 422-423)
        - Site (Box 117, Folder 424-430)
        - Voyage (Box 117, Folder 431-435)
        - Unidentified (Box 117, Folder 436-439)
    - Esashi, 1896
      - General (Box 118, Folder 440-449)
      - Esashi expedition, 1896
        - Coronas (Box 118, Folder 450-455)
        - Equipment (Box 118, Folder 456-457)
        - Equipment (Box 119, Folder 458-470)
        - Site (Box 119, Folder 471-476)
        - Voyage (Box 120, Folder 477-487)
    - Fuji, 1887
      - Diagrams and maps (Box 120, Folder 488-492)
      - Views (Box 121, Folder 493-499)
    - Shirakawa
      - General (Box 121, Folder 500-502)
      - Eclipse expedition (Box 121)
      - Writings (Box 121, Folder 503-505)
      - Group portraits (Box 121, Folder 506-507)
    - Panama
      - General, 1907 (Box 122, Folder 508-526)
      - Panama Canal (Box 123, Folder 527-546)
      - Panama Canal (Box 124, Folder 547-564)
      - Panama Canal (Box 125, Folder 565-567)
    - Philippines
      - Cebu (Box 125, Folder 568-581)
      - Corregidor (Box 125, Folder 582-586)
      - Jolo (Box 126, Folder 587-593)
      - Manilla (Box 126, Folder 594-605)
      - Manilla (Box 127, Folder 606-609)
      - Map (Box 127, Folder 610)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified (#620 destroyed, print available) (Box 127, Folder 611-620)
    - Russia
      - Eclipse expedition, 1914
        - Bobinsky estate (Box 127, Folder 621-623)
        - Corona (Box 127, Folder 624)
    - Siam
      - General (Box 128, Folder 625-637)
    - Spain
      - Granada (Box 129, Folder 638-645)
      - Seville (Box 129, Folder 646-648)
    - Other nations and areas
      - Algiers (Box 129, Folder 649-651)
      - Gibraltar (Box 129, Folder 652-654)
      - Malta (Box 129, Folder 655-657)
      - Tunis (Box 129, Folder 658-664)
      - Tunis (Box 130, Folder 665-684)
      - Tunis-ruins (Box 131, Folder 685-701)
      - Unidentified (Box 132, Folder 702-713)
    - Sweden
      - General (Box 132, Folder 714-719)
      - General (Box 133, Folder 720-725)
      - Olympics, 1912
        - American team aboard S. S. Finland (Box 133, Folder 726-733)
        - Athletes—portraits (Box 133, Folder 734-737)
        - Athletes—portraits (Box 134, Folder 738-749)
        - Events
          - Crew (Box 134, Folder 750-751)
          - Gymnastics (Box 134, Folder 752-755)
          - Gymnastics (Box 135, Folder 756-759)
          - Javelin (Box 135, Folder 760)
          - Track and Field (Box 135, Folder 761-771)
          - Shotput (Box 135, Folder 772-773)
          - Shotput (Box 136, Folder 774-775)
          - Swimming (Box 136, Folder 776-778)
        - Opening ceremonies (Box 137, Folder 779-785)
        - Stadium (Box 137, Folder 786-790)
        - Unidentified (Box 137, Folder 791-795)
    - United States
      - Florida—Congrès International de Géographie slides, 1931 (Box 137, Folder 796-807)
      - Florida—Congrès International de Géographie slides, 1931 (Box 138, Folder 808-823)
      - Hawaii
        - General (Box 139, Folder 824-842)
        - General (Box 140, Folder 843-862)
        - General (Box 141, Folder 863-865)
        - Field, Kate (Box 141, Folder 866)
      - Massachusetts
        - Amherst College
          - Athletic events (Box 141, Folder 867-873)
          - Buildings (Box 141, Folder 874-880)
          - Buildings (Box 142, Folder 881-889)
          - Campus views (Box 142, Folder 890-899)
          - Campus views (Box 143, Folder 900-904)
          - Fraternity houses (Box 143, Folder 905-911)
          - Portraits—President and Mrs. Harris; "Old Doc," 1908 (Box 143, Folder 912-913)
        - Fitchburg
          - Balloon trip (Box 143, Folder 914-918)
          - Balloon trip (Box 144, Folder 919-934)
    - West Indies
      - Barbados (Box 145, Folder 935-942)
    - Astronomy and textbook material
      - Book illustrations- New Astronomy (Box 145, Folder 943-951)
      - Book illustrations- New Astronomy (Box 146, Folder 952-967)
      - Comets
        - Diagrams (Box 147, Folder 968-972)
        - Comet of 1843 (Box 147, Folder 973)
        - Comet of 1861 (Box 147, Folder 974)
        - [illegible] (Box 147, Folder 975)
        - Donati's Comet (Box 147, Folder 976)
        - Halley's Comet (Box 147, Folder 977)
        - Swift's Comet (Box 147, Folder 978)
        - Unidentified (Box 147, Folder 979-985)
      - Eclipses
        - Coronas—dated
          - 1868-1882 (Box 147, Folder 986-989)
          - 1885-1886 (Box 148, Folder 990-94)
          - 1889 (Box 148, Folder 995-1001)
          - 1893 (Box 148, Folder 1002)
          - 1898 (Box 148, Folder 1003-1006)
          - 1914 (Box 149, Folder 1007-1008)
        - Coronas—Undated
          - Coronas—Undated (Box 150, Folder 1031-1061)
          - Textbook material (Box 151, Folder 1062-1071)
          - Equipment (Box 151, Folder 1072-1081)
          - Equipment (Box 152, Folder 1082-1089)
          - Maps (Box 152, Folder 1090-1091)
          - Observatories and telescopes
            - Africa, South—Capetown (Box 152, Folder 1092-1097)
            - France—Paris (Box 153, Folder 1093-1099)
            - Germany—Pottsdam (Box 153, Folder 1100)
        - United States
          - California—Lick Observatory (Box 153, Folder 1101-1107)
          - Massachusetts—Amherst (Box 153, Folder 1108-1113)
          - Massachusetts—Cambridge, Harvard University (Box 153, Folder 1114)
        - Unidentified (Box 154, Folder 1115-1123)
      - Planets and satellites
        - Mars (Box 154, Folder 1124-1132)
        - Meteors (Box 155, Folder 1133-1135)
        - Moon (Box 155, Folder 1136-1143)
        - Saturn (Box 155, Folder 1144-1146)
        - Venus 1882 Transit (Box 155, Folder 1147-1149)
        - Unidentified (Box 156, Folder 1150-1151)
      - Spectra (Box 156, Folder 1152-1161)
      - Stars
        - Constellations (Box 156, Folder 1162-1165)
        - Constellations (Box 157, Folder 1166-1167)
        - Nebulae (Box 157, Folder 1168-1172)
        - Unidentified (Box 157, Folder 1173-1183)
      - Sun—sunspots (Box 158, Folder 1184-1187)
  - Oversize
    - 6 1/2" x 8 1/2,"
      - (17-19) (Box 159)
      - 55—(71-72) (Box 159)
      - 57—(134;143) (Box 159)
      - 59—201 (Box 159)
      - 60—(204-208) (Box 159)
      - 72—(496-501) (Box 159)
      - 73—(511; 517-519; 528-536) (Box 159)
      - 74—(583-603) (Box 160)
      - 75—(604-609; 613-616) (Box 160)
      - 82—(802-807; 810-812; 814-819) (Box 161)
      - 83—847 (Box 161)
      - 85—(895-900; 906-911) (Box 161)
      - 86—(924-953) (Box 162)
      - 88—1001 (Box 163)
      - 88—(1004-1006)
        See: Box 1
      - 88—(1024-1027) (Box 163)
      - 89—(1053-1064; 1069-1073) (Box 163)
    - 8"x10"
      - 62—256 (Box 164)
      - 72—(487-489) (Box 164)
      - 76—(641; 649-651) (Box 164)
      - 80—(751-758) (Box 164)
      - 80—(759-760) (Box 165)
      - 82—820 (Box 165)
      - 83—846 (Box 165)
      - 85—(893-894) (Box 165)
      - 85—(903-905) (Box 165)
      - 86—966 (Box 165)
      - 88—1003 (Box 165)
      - 91—(1101-1105) (Box 165)
    - 10"x12"
      - 1141-1153—Negatives for photographs in SERIES II, Box 43, Album no. 19 [Esashi, Japan 1896] (Box 166)
      - 1154—Dutch East Indies expedition, group portrait (1901) (Box 167)
      - 1155—Dutch East Indies expedition, tin mines (1901) (Box 167)
      - 1156-1158—Amherst College, "New Observatory," cornerstone ceremonies (1903) (Box 167)
      - 1159—Amherst College, "New Observatory," workmen at construction site (1903) (Box 167)
    - 12" x 15" See: Glass negative folio 172B
      - 1160—Esashi, Japan expedition, 1896(?), cracked negative of buildings and people (Box 167)
      - 1161—Esashi, Japan expedition, 1896:(?), chipped negative of group including David Peck Todd, Mabel Loomis Todd, and Millicent Todd (Bingham) (Box 167)
  - Prints
    - Glass negatives (Box 168)
    - Africa, west
      - Angloa, 1889
        - 63—(260-263; 265-277) (Box 168)
        - 64—(278-285) (Box 168)
      - Ascension Island
        - 64—(286-87) (Box 168)
      - Azores
        - 64—288 (Box 168)
      - Cape Ledo(?)
        - 64—290 (Box 168)
      - Loanda
        - 64—(292-294) (Box 168)
      - Rio Quanza
        - 64—295 (Box 168)
      - St. Helena
        - 65—(316-317) (Box 168)
      - Dutch East Indies
        - Singkep
          - 66—(332-337; 342-346) (Box 168)
          - 67—(348-353; 356-362) (Box 168)
          - 67—(366; 369; 371-373) (Box 168)
          - 68—(374-377; 379-380) (Box 168)
    - Ecuador
      - 68—(381-396; 398) (Box 168)
      - 69—(399-405) (Box 168)
    - India
      - 71—(450-473) (Box 168)
    - Japan
      - General and Esashi, 1896
        - 72—(488-489; 491-494; 496-499; 502-463) (Box 169)
        - 72—(506-507) (Box 169)
        - 73—(511-517; 528-532) (Box 169)
        - 74—(582; 585-588; 590-591; 593-594; 596; 599; 600-602) (Box 169)
        - 75—(604-605; 610; 613) (Box 169)
      - Fuji, 1882
        - 75—(614; 616-374) (Box 169)
      - Shirakawa, 1887
        - 76—(635-650; 652-655; 657-658) (Box 169)
        - 79—(712-714) (Box 169)
      - Peru, 1913
        - 79—(715-722) (Box 169)
        - 80—(723-735) (Box 169)
      - Philippine Islands, 1901
        - 80—(740-750) (Box 169)
      - Russia, 1914
        - 80—751 (Box 169)
    - Spain
      - 81—(765-769; 771) (Box 169)
    - Tunis
      - 81—(780-781) (Box 169)
      - 82—(793-94; 796-801) (Box 169)
    - United States
      - California
        - 82-(802-817; 819) (Box 169)
      - Florida
        - 82—(820; 822) (Box 169)
      - Hawaii, 1896
        - 83—(827-829; 831-838; 844-845) (Box 169)
      - Massachusetts
        - Amherst
          - 83—(847-850; 852-853) (Box 169)
          - 84—(854-864) (Box 169)
          - 85—(882-891) (Box 169)
          - Amherst College (Box 169)
          - 85—(895-898) (Box 169)
          - 85—901 (Box 169)
          - Unidentified (Box 169)
          - 85—(902-911) (Box 169)
    - West Indies
      - 85—(912-915) (Box 169)
    - Astronomy and textbook material
      - Asteroids
        - 86—(916-917) (Box 170)
      - Book Illustrations— New Astronomy
        - 86—(918-923) (Box 170)
        - 86—(924-932; 938-942; 945-953) (Box 170)
      - Comets
        - 86—(955-957; 959-964) (Box 170)
      - Eclipses
        - Archaeological subjects
          - 87—(967-969) (Box 170)
        - Castori
          - 87—(970-978) (Box 170)
        - Coronas
          - 87—(982-990) (Box 170)
          - 88—(993-999; 1003; 1010-1014; 1016-1026) (Box 170)
          - 89—(1028-1035) (Box 170)
        - Instruments
          - 89—(1036-1044) (Box 170)
        - Observatories and telescopes
          - 89—(1045-1047; 1053-1063; 1065-1067; 1069-1075) (Box 170)
        - Planets and satellites
          - 90—(1076-1094) (Box 170)
        - Spectra
          - 90—(1097-1100) (Box 170)
        - Stars
          - 91—(1101-1114) (Box 170)
        - X-Ray plates
          - 91—(1120-1031) (Box 170)
        - Zodiac drawings
          - 92—(1132-1140) (Box 170)
    - Lantern slides (Box 170)
    - Places
      - Africa, North
        - Tripoli, 1900
          - General 93—(1-2) (Box 171)
          - 95—(45-47) (Box 171)
          - Eclipse 95—(48-52) (Box 171)
        - Tripoli, 1905
          - General 95—(53-61) (Box 171)
          - 96—(71-74) (Box 171)
          - Eclipse 96—(75; 97-84) (Box 171)
        - Africa, South
          - Capetown 97—(87-88) (Box 171)
          - Kimberly, 1874 (Box 171)
          - 97—(90-97) (Box 171)
          - General 98—(100-102) (Box 171)
      - Africa, West
        - General 99—(104-116) (Box 171)
        - Angola, 1889
          - Pensacola cruise—maps and newspapers
            - 100—(132-134; 136-137; 139; 141; 144) (Box 171)
            - 100—(146; 149) (Box 171)
          - Ascension Island 101-150 (Box 171)
          - Azores 101—(155-157) (Box 171)
          - Rio Quanzo 102-165 (Box 171)
          - St. Helena
            - 102—(169-171) (Box 171)
            - 103—(172-173) (Box 171)
          - Sierra Leone 104-196 (Box 171)
          - Canada 104—(198-200) (Box 171)
          - 105—(201-206) (Box 171)
          - Chile 108—(255-257) (Box 171)
          - Dutch East Indies
            - 109—(276-279; 282) (Box 171)
            - 110—292 (Box 171)
          - Egypt 111—(314-315) (Box 171)
          - Germany 113—(360-363) (Box 171)
          - [illegible] (Box 171)
      - Japan
        - "In Ainuland"—Mabel Loomis Todd lecture
          - 115—(389-391; 397-403) (Box 171)
        - Esashi
          - General 118—(440-445) (Box 171)
          - Coronas 118—(450-455) (Box 171)
          - Expedition site 119—(475-476) (Box 171)
          - Voyage 120—487 (Box 171)
        - Fuji 121—(493-494) (Box 171)
        - Shirakawa, 1887 121—(500-501) (Box 171)
        - Panama
          - General 122—(508-510; 512-547) (Box 171)
          - Canal 122—(518-526)
            - 123—(527-546) (Box 171)
            - 124—(547-564) (Box 171)
            - 125—(565-567) (Box 171)
        - Philippines
          - Cebu 125—(568-580) (Box 171)
          - Corregidor 125—(582-586) (Box 171)
          - Manila 126—594 (Box 171)
          - Miscellaneous/[illegible] (Box 171)
    - Places
      - United States
        - Florida 137—(796-807)
          - 138—(808-23) (Box 171)
        - Hawaii 140—(856-862)
          - 141—(863-865) (Box 171)
        - Massachusetts (Box 171)
        - Amherst College
          - 141—(867-869) (Box 171)
          - 141—(874-880) (Box 171)
          - 142—(881-888) (Box 171)
          - 142—(890-899) (Box 171)
          - 143—(900-913) (Box 171)
    - Oversize
      - Amherst College, "New Observatory" (Box 171, Folder 1156-1159)
        See: box 172C
        General
        See: box 3
  - Film Negatives
    - Lantern slides (Box 171)
    - Places
      - United States
        - Massachusetts (Box 172, Folder 12)
          867-932
          see also: box 1, folder 11
        - 1004-1006, negatives (Box 172A)
        - 1160-1061, negatives (Box 172B)
        - 1156-1059 prints (Box 172C)
- SMALL FOLIOS, Series IV; 12; folios
  - Amherst, Massachusetts and Environs
    - Amherst College
      - Appelton Cabinet: Hitchcock Ichnological Museum (Box 173)
      - Barnet Hall: gymnasium (Box 173)
      - Chapel: interior (Box 173)
      - Chapel and dormitories (Box 173)
      - Chapel Tower (Box 173)
      - Chi Phi Lodge (Box 173)
      - College Hall (Box 173)
      - East College (Box 173)
      - Mather Art Collection (Box 173)
      - North College, Chapel, South College, Appelton Cabinet (Box 173)
      - Observatory: laying of cornerstone 1903 (Box 173)
      - Pratt Gymnasium (Box 173)
      - President's House, Library, College Hall (Box 173)
      - Walker Hall: pre-1882 (Box 173)
      - Walker Hall: post-1882, after fire (Box 173)
      - Williston Hall (Box 173)